{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Glass Block Installation Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/99993/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":99993,"taskName":"Glass Blocks - Install","taskDescription":"Install Glass Blocks","xmTaskDescriptor":"Glass Block Installation Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":105,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"glass blocks privacy window shower","textMessagingName":"Install Glass Blocks","rolloverLongDesc":"Glass blocks are used to create translucent masonry walls in both interior \u0026 exterior applications. They are also used to brick in basement windows to create relatively burglar-proof openings that still supply light. This category includes plastic blocks or Acrylic that simulate glass blocks.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes interior, exterior \u0026 filling in windows.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Glass or Acrylic Blocks.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Glass Block Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Glass Block Window","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":74,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Glass Blocks Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Glass Blocks - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Glass Block Installation Project","urlName":"Glass-Blocks-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Glass Block Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews \u0026 Costs","searchKeywords":"glass,blocks,privacy,window,shower","emcCategoryOid":-12073,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":783,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/99993/":{"taskOID":99993,"originalTaskOID":99993,"setID":783,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5654,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want the glass/acrylic block installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior wall/partition","answerDisplayText":"Interior wall/partition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6738,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall between interior and exterior","answerDisplayText":"Wall between interior and exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior wall/partition","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wall/partition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5649,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5655,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6454,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional glass block","answerDisplayText":"Traditional glass block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Acrylic block","answerDisplayText":"Acrylic block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3780,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Maximum light","answerDisplayText":"Maximum light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3781,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Maximum privacy","answerDisplayText":"Maximum privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4617,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Patterned design","answerDisplayText":"Patterned design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2667,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Frosted glass/acrylic","answerDisplayText":"Frosted glass/acrylic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1490,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Colored glass/acrylic","answerDisplayText":"Colored glass/acrylic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6670,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vent in solid window/wall","answerDisplayText":"Vent in solid window/wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1744,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Curved wall","answerDisplayText":"Curved wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":829,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Arched top","answerDisplayText":"Arched top","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1756,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Custom design","answerDisplayText":"Custom design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5654,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want the glass/acrylic block installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior wall/partition","answerDisplayText":"Interior wall/partition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6738,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall between interior and exterior","answerDisplayText":"Wall between interior and exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior wall/partition","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wall/partition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5649,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior wall/partition","answerDisplayText":"Interior wall/partition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6738,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall between interior and exterior","answerDisplayText":"Wall between interior and exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior wall/partition","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wall/partition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5649,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Shower stall","answerDisplayText":"Shower stall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5655,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6454,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional glass block","answerDisplayText":"Traditional glass block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Acrylic block","answerDisplayText":"Acrylic block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3780,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Maximum light","answerDisplayText":"Maximum light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3781,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Maximum privacy","answerDisplayText":"Maximum privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4617,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Patterned design","answerDisplayText":"Patterned design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2667,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Frosted glass/acrylic","answerDisplayText":"Frosted glass/acrylic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1490,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Colored glass/acrylic","answerDisplayText":"Colored glass/acrylic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6670,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vent in solid window/wall","answerDisplayText":"Vent in solid window/wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1744,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Curved wall","answerDisplayText":"Curved wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":829,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Arched top","answerDisplayText":"Arched top","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1756,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Custom design","answerDisplayText":"Custom design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6454,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional glass block","answerDisplayText":"Traditional glass block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Acrylic block","answerDisplayText":"Acrylic block","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3780,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Maximum light","answerDisplayText":"Maximum light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3781,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Maximum privacy","answerDisplayText":"Maximum privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4617,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Patterned design","answerDisplayText":"Patterned design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2667,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Frosted glass/acrylic","answerDisplayText":"Frosted glass/acrylic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1490,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Colored glass/acrylic","answerDisplayText":"Colored glass/acrylic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6670,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vent in solid window/wall","answerDisplayText":"Vent in solid window/wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1744,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Curved wall","answerDisplayText":"Curved wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":829,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Arched top","answerDisplayText":"Arched top","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1756,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Custom design","answerDisplayText":"Custom design","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}